Blackboard Course Management System Records UA229
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts organizations, 2002 -- 2011; UA229.004; 2.95 Linear Feet
  - TENS GK12, 2003 -- 2006; UA229.004.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Film Works, 2005 -- 2010; UA229.004.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - TUTV-23, 2007 -- 2009; UA229.004.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Water: Systems, Society and Science, 2003 -- 2004; UA229.004.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - University Awards Committee, 2005 -- 2010; UA229.004.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Urban and Environmental Policy and Planning, 2005 -- 2011; UA229.004.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - WSSS: Urban Water Management Group, 2005 -- 2010; UA229.004.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - Yahon, Ronnee, 2007; UA229.004.004.00024 (Box 4)
    Materials for Legal and Ethical Issues in Clinical Research, Ethico-Legal Aspects of Bioscience, and Student Society for Stem Cell Research.
- Additional accessions, UA229.000187
  - Engineering Photos, 2005 -- 2011; UA229-001